domainz.in 2013-11-07

# Privacy Policy

**Register any new Domain& Get Starter Web Hosting Worth Rs.300 absolutely Free! (applicable on all domain extensions).**   
**Our domain registration pricing is up-to 20% lesser as compared to other companies in India (Click Here to See)**   
| | |  | Privacy Policy  
---  

> In an effort to protect our clients' and site visitors privacy and rights, DOMAINZ.IN has established a Privacy Policy which explains what information we gather on visitors and what we do with information that we gather.   
> This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which DOMAINZ.IN collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a "User"). 
> 
> **Privacy**
> 
> Users' privacy is very important to DOMAINZ.IN. We are committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to DOMAINZ.IN. 
> 
> **The Information We Collect**
> 
> DOMAINZ.IN collects personally identifiable information from Users through online forms for ordering products and services. We may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. 
> 
> **How We Use Information**
> 
> DOMAINZ.IN may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by DOMAINZ.IN and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with DOMAINZ.IN and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. At no time will DOMAINZ.IN's database of users ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists. Personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to our business partners without your prior consent, except that we will disclose the information we collect to third parties when, in our good faith judgment, we are obligated to do so under applicable laws.  

---  
Register Domain Name, Domain Registration, Web Hosting, Unlimited Hosting, Reseller Hosting. Register .com, .in, .co.in, .org, .net, .info domains   
A website by Karmath InfoTech Pvt. Ltd. ® 2005 - 2013   
 |  Register Domain | Bulk Domain Search | Transfer Domain | Domain Pricing | Web Hosting | Reseller Web Hosting | Website Builder   
Contact Us |  Our Bank Accounts | Check Whois | Usage Policy | Mail Policy | Privacy Policy | Support Policy | Reward Program   
Windows Web Hosting | [Free SMS](http://www.atrochatro.com/) |  [SMS Reseller, Resell SMS, Bulk SMS, SMS Short Code](http://www.beep7.com/)  
   
Page took 0.015713 seconds to load.
